<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.bluesabre.SgtLauncher</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
  <name>SGT Puzzles Collection</name>
  <summary>Launcher for Simon Tatham's Portable Puzzle Collection</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Starter til Simon Tatham's transportable opgavesamling</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Starter für Simon Tathams Portable Puzzle Collection</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Lanzadpr de la colección portátil de puzles de Simon Tatham</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Käynnistin Simon Tathamin siirrettävälle pulmapelikokoelmalle</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Lanceur pour la collection de puzzles portables de Simon Tatham</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Leistukas, skirtas Simon'o Tatham'o perkeliamų galvosūkių kolekcijai</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms">Pelancar untuk Himpunan Teka-Teki Mudah Alih milik Simon Tatham</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ms@Arab">ڤلنچر اونتوق هيمڤونن تکا-تکي موده اليه ميليق Simon Tatham</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Starter voor Simon Tathams Draagbare Puzzelverzameling</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Program uruchamiający gry z Kolekcji Gier Logicznych Simona Tathama</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Lançador para a colecção portátil de quebra-cabeças de  Simon Tatham</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Startare för Simon Tathams portabla pusselsamling</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">Simon Tatham 可移植益智集合的简易启动器</summary>

  <description>
    <p>SGT Puzzles Collection is a simple-to-use launcher for Simon Tatham's Portable Puzzle Collection.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">SGT-opgavesamling er en letanvendelig starter til Simon Tatham's transportable opgavesamling.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">SGT Puzzles Collection ist ein einfach zu bedienender Starter für Simon Tathams Portable Puzzle Collection.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">La colección de puzles SGT es un lanzador simple de usar para la colección portátil de puzles de Simon Tatham.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">SGT pulmapelikokoelma on helppokäyttöinen käynnistin Simon Tathamin siirrettävälle pulmapelikokoelmalle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">La collection de puzzles SGT est un lanceur facile à utiliser pour la collection de puzzles portables de Simon Tatham</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">SGT galvosūkių kolekcija yra paprastas naudoti leistukas, skirtas Simon'o Tatham'o perkeliamų galvosūkių kolekcijai.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Himpunan Teka-Teki SGT ialah pelancar yang mudah untuk digunakan bagi Himpunan Teka-Teki Mudah Alih milik Simon Tatham.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">هيمڤونن تکا-تکي SGT اياله ڤلنچر يڠ موده اونتوق دݢوناکن باݢي هيمڤونن تکا-تکي موده اليه ميليق Simon Tatham.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">SGT Puzzelverzameling is een eenvoudige starter voor Simon Tathams Draagbare Puzzelverzameling</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">SGT Puzzles Collection jest prostym w użyciu programem uruchamiającym gry z kolekcji gier logicznych Simona Tathama.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Colecção Quebra-cabeças SGT é um lançador simples de usar para a colecção portátil de quebra-cabeças de Simon Tatham</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">SGT Pusselsamling är en startare som är enkel att använda för Simon Tathams portabla pusselsamling.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">SGT 益智集合是 Simon Tatham 的可移植益智集合的简易启动器。</p>
    <p>The collection is presented as a related but diverse set of logic games. Each game is displayed in the launcher window with simplified controls.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Samlingen præsenteres som et relaterede men forskelligartede sæt logiske spil. Hvert spil vises i startervinduet med simple styringer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Sammlung präsentiert sich als eine Reihe von verwandten, aber dennoch vielfältigen Logikspielen. Jedes Spiel wird im Starter-Fenster mit einer vereinfachten Steuerung angezeigt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">La colección se presenta como un conjunto de juegos relacionados pero diversos de lógica. Cada juego se muestra en la ventana del lanzador con controles simplificados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kokoelma on esitelty yhtenä kokonaisuutena ja sisältää erilaisia logiikkapelejä. Jokainen peli esitetään käynnistinikkunassa yksinkertaisella tavalla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cette collection est composée d'une série de jeux de logiques liés, mais différents. Chaque jeu est affiché dans la fenêtre du lanceur avec des contrôles simplifiés.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Kolekcija yra pateikiama kaip susijusių, tačiau įvairialypių loginių žaidimų rinkinys. Kiekvienas žaidimas yra rodomas leistuko lange su supaprastintais valdikliais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms">Himpunan ditunjukkan sebagai set permainan logik yang berkaitan tetapi pelbagai. Setiap permainan dipaparkan di tetingkap pelancar dengan menu kawalan yang dipermudahkan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">هيمڤونن دتونجوقکن سباݢاي سيت ڤرماٴينن لوݢيک يڠ برکاٴيتن تتاڤي ڤلباݢاي. ستياڤ ڤرماٴينن دڤاڤرکن دتتيڠکڤ ڤلنچر دڠن مينو کاولن يڠ دڤرمودهکن.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De verzameling bevat gelijkaardige, maar van elkaar verschillende, spellen. Elk spel wordt met vereenvoudigde besturing in de starter getoond.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kolekcja zawiera różnorodne gry logiczne. Każda jest wyświetlana w tym oknie z uproszczonym sterowaniem.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">A coleção é apresentada como jogos relacionados, mas diversos, com jogos de lógica. Cada jogo é exibido na janela do lançador com controlos simplificados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Samlingen presenteras som en relaterad men mångsidig uppsättning logikspel. Varje spel visas i startfönstret med förenklade kontroller.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">该集合以一组相关但多样的逻辑游戏形式呈现。每个游戏都以简化的控件显示在启动器窗口中。</p>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.bluesabre.SgtLauncher.desktop</launchable>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>The launcher window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Startervinduet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Das Starter-Fenster</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">La ventana lanzadora</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Käynnistinikkuna</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La fenêtre du lanceur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Leistuko langas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ms">Tetingkap pelancar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ms@Arab">تتيڠکڤ ڤلنچر</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Het startvenster</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Okno programu uruchamiającego</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">A janela do lançador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Startfönstret</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">启动器窗口</caption>
      <image>https://screenshots.bluesabre.org/sgt-launcher/sgt-launcher-01.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Playing a short game of Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Spiller er hurtigt spil Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Ein kurzes Spiel mit Galaxien spielen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Jugar una partida corta de Galaxias</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Keskeneräinen lyhyt Galaxies-peli</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Joue un jeu court de Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Žaidžiamas trumpas "Galaxies" žaidimas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ms">Bermain permainan pendek bernama Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ms@Arab">برماٴين ڤرماٴينن ڤينديق برنام Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Speel een kort Galaxies-spel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Krótka rozgrywka w Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Jogando um curto jogo de Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Spela en kort omgång av Galaxies</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра в коротку гру Галактики</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh_CN">玩一个简短的星系游戏</caption>
      <image>https://screenshots.bluesabre.org/sgt-launcher/sgt-launcher-02.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/bluesabre/sgt-launcher</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/bluesabre/sgt-launcher/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://bluesabre.org/donate</url>
  <url type="translate">https://www.transifex.com/bluesabreorg/sgt-puzzles-collection/</url>

  <provides>
    <binary>sgt-launcher</binary>
  </provides>

  <releases>
    <release version="0.2.7" date="2021-09-11">
      <description>
        <p>This release includes improved support for various desktop environments and updated translations.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.6" date="2020-07-30">
      <description>
        <p>This release includes some minor fixes and updated translations.</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Udgivelsen inkluderer nogle mindre rettelser og opdaterede oversættelser.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Diese Version enthält einige kleinere Korrekturen und aktualisierte Übersetzungen.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Terbitan ini mempunyai beberapa pembaikian kecil dan pengemaskinian terjemahan.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">تربيتن اين ممڤوڽاٴي ببراڤ ڤمباٴيقين کچيل دان ڤڠمسکينين ترجمهن.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat kleine foutoplossingen en bijgewerkte vertalingen.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">To wydanie zawiera kilka drobnych poprawek i zaktualizowanych tłumaczeń.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Denna version innehåller några mindre korrigeringar och uppdaterade översättningar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">此版本包括一些小修复和翻译更新。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.5" date="2020-02-19">
      <description>
        <p>This release features improved game launching and adds a bug reporting link to the menu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Udgivelsen indeholder forbedret spilstart og der er tilføjet et fejlrapporteringslink i menuen.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Diese Version bietet einen verbesserten Spielstart und fügt dem Menü einen Link zum Melden von Fehlern hinzu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="lt">Šioje laidoje patobulintas žaidimo paleidimas ir į meniu pridėta pranešimo apie klaidas nuoroda.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Terbitan ini mengetengahkan pelancaran permainan yang ditambahbaik dan menambah pautan pelaporan pepijat ke dalam menu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">تربيتن اين مڠتڠهکن ڤلنچرن ڤرماٴينن يڠ دتمبهباٴيق دان منمبه ڤاٴوتن ڤلاڤورن کدالم مينو.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Deze uitgave bevat verbeteringen omtrent het opstarten van spellen en een bugmeldingslink in hen menu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Ta wersja zawiera ulepszone uruchamianie gry i dodaje link do zgłaszania błędów do menu.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Denna version har förbättrad spelstart och lägger till en länk till felrapportering i menyn.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">这个版本的特点是改进了游戏启动，并在菜单中添加了错误报告链接。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.4" date="2018-04-11">
      <description>
        <p>This is a minor translations-only release.</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Det er en mindre udgivelse kun til oversættelser.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Dies ist eine kleinere Version, die nur Übersetzungen enthält.</p>
        <p xml:lang="lt">Tai yra nedidelė laida su atnaujintais vertimais.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Ini terbitan kecil yang hanya mengandungi kemaskini terjemahan.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">اين تربيتن کچيل يڠ هاڽ مڠندوڠي کمسکيني ترجمهن.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Dit is een kleine uitgave die alleen bijgewerkte vertalingen bevat.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">To jest niewielkie wydanie tylko tłumaczenia.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Detta är en mindre version endast med nya översättningar.</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Це є невеликий випуск лише для перекладу.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">这是一个次要的翻译更新版本。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.3" date="2017-10-03">
      <description>
        <p>The Preferences menu item has been removed and several translations have been included.</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Menupunktet Præferencer er blevet fjernet og adskillige oversættelser er inkluderet.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Der Menüpunkt "Voreinstellungen" wurde entfernt und mehrere Übersetzungen wurden hinzugefügt.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Le menu préférences a été supprimé, et des traductions ont étés incluses.</p>
        <p xml:lang="lt">Nuostatų meniu buvo pašalintas ir buvo įtraukti keli nauji programos vertimai.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Item menu Keutamaan telah dibuang dan beberapa terjemahan telah disertakan.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">ايتم مينو کأوتاماٴن تله دبواڠ دان ببراڤ ترجمهن تله دسرتاکن.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Het voorkeurenmenu-item is verwijderd en er zijn verschillende vertalingen toegevoegd.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Element menu Preferencje został usunięty i dołączono kilka tłumaczeń.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">O item de menu Preferências foi removido e várias traduções foram incluídas.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Menyalternativet Inställningar har tagits bort och flera översättningar har inkluderats.</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Пункт меню "Налаштування" видалено, та було додано кілька перекладів.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">首选项菜单项已被删除，并包含了多个翻译。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.2" date="2017-01-29">
      <description>
        <p>Non-existent launchers are no longer displayed. The application launcher now links to the correct binary.</p>
        <p xml:lang="da">Ikkeeksisterende startere vises ikke længere. Programstarteren linker nu til den korrekte binær.</p>
        <p xml:lang="de">Nicht existierende Starter werden nicht mehr angezeigt. Der Anwendungsstarter verweist nun auf die richtige Binärdatei.</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Los lanzadores inexistentes ya no se muestran. El lanzador de aplicaciones ahora enlaza con el binario correcto.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fi">Käynnistimiä joita ei ole olemassa ei enää näytetä. Sovelluskäynnistin on nyt linkitetty oikeaan binääritiedostoon.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Les lanceurs non-existants ne sont plus affichés. Le lanceur de l'application pointe désormais vers les binaires corrects.</p>
        <p xml:lang="lt">Leistukai, kurių nėra, daugiau neberodomi. Programos leistukas dabar susieja su teisinga dvejetaine.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms">Pelancar yang tidak wujud kini tidak akan dipaparkan lagi. Pelancar aplikasi kini dipautkan ke perduaan yang betul.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ms@Arab">ڤلنچر يڠ تيدق وجود کيني تيدق اکن دڤاڤرکن لاݢي. ڤلنچر اڤليکاسي کيني دڤاٴوتکن کڤردواٴن يڠ بتول.</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Niet-bestaande starters worden niet langer getoond. De starter verwijst nu naar de juiste uitvoerbare bestanden.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pl">Nieistniejące skróty nie są już wyświetlane. Program uruchamiający kieruje teraz do prawidłowych plików.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt">Os lançadores inexistentes já não são exibidos. O lançador da aplicação vincula-se agora ao binário correto.</p>
        <p xml:lang="sv">Icke-existerande startare visas inte längre. Applikationsstartaren länkar nu till rätt binär.</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh_CN">不存在的启动器将不再显示。 现在，应用程序启动器已链接到正确的二进制文件。</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>